[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river rises in the northwestern Czech Republic, flows through Germany and into the North Sea?", "correct_answer": "Elbe", "incorrect_answers": ["Viskan", "Morava", "Oste"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What shade of the blue color is also called angel blue?", "correct_answer": "Light blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Cerulean", "Cyan", "Ultramarine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sings the title song in the movie For Your Eyes Only?", "correct_answer": "Sheena Easton", "incorrect_answers": ["Kim Carnes", "Deborah Harry", "Hazel O Connor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the pilot of SpaceShipOne, the spaceplane that completed the first privately funded human spaceflight?", "correct_answer": "Mike Melvill", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Siebold", "Doug Shane", "Brian Binnie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary Hollywood actress portrayed Queen Cleopatra in the 1963 movie Cleopatra, one of the most expensive movies in history?", "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Taylor", "incorrect_answers": ["Ginger Rogers", "Greta Garbo", "Marilyn Monroe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What month has the pearl for its birthstone and the rose for its birth flower?", "correct_answer": "June", "incorrect_answers": ["May", "July", "March"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the narrator of Ken Keseys novel One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest, which was adapted into a multi-Oscar winning film?", "correct_answer": "Chief Bromden", "incorrect_answers": ["Randle McMurphy", "Nurse Ratched", "Billy Bibbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from The Raven says the line, Dont you ever fuckin die? when he confronts Eric Draven?", "correct_answer": "Funboy", "incorrect_answers": ["Top Dollar", "T-Bird", "Gideon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whose wife was Sarah according to the Hebrew Bible and the Quran?", "correct_answer": "Abrahams", "incorrect_answers": ["Ishmaels", "Noahs", "Isaacs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What former All-Pro linebacker appeared in the movie Johnny dangerously as Arthur?", "correct_answer": "Dick Butkus", "incorrect_answers": ["Merlin Olsen", "Lawrence Taylor", "Mike Singletary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following colors cannot be a pure spectral color?", "correct_answer": "Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Cyan", "Yellow", "Orange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturns magnetic field is stronger than Earths.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]